mellanox.com 2014-12-01

# Legal Privacy: Mellanox Technologies

## Legal & Privacy Policy

**_Policy last updated_** :  July 22, 2014  

This is the website (“Website”) of Mellanox Technologies, Ltd. (collectively with all subsidiaries, “Mellanox”).  Your privacy is very important to us.  The purpose of this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is to inform you about our policy and our practices regarding the collection and use of information from visitors to this Website.  By accessing or using this Website, you agree to all of the terms and conditions set forth in this Privacy Policy.  

#### **_Non-Personal Information  
_**

This Website automatically collects certain data that is not personally-identifiable; this may include your IP address, the URL you came from, the time and date of your visit, where you went on this Website, your browser type, your operating system, and the URL you went to when you left this Website.  This information is analyzed to help us understand our audience, business, customers, sales, traffic patterns, performance and related website information, and improve this Website, our products, and services. 

#### **_Personal Information  
_**

We do not collect any personally-identifiable information about you except when you specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis.  For example, if you choose to contact us through this Website, however, we will collect your contact information. In addition, if you are a Mellanox partner or customer and have been granted access to the secure portion of our Website using your username and password, or require help desk support services, we may collect personally identifiable information such as your name, phone number, your company name, mailing address, email address, country and region in which you reside and may maintain a database of this information in order to service customer and partner requests and inquiries.  Such personal information is used to provide the information or service you request, send pertinent marketing promotions to you as well as to help us understand our audience, business, customers, sales, traffic patterns, performance and related Website information, and improve this Website, products and services.   ****  

Since access to certain Mellanox web pages requires username and password, we recommend that you do not divulge your username and password to anyone and follow safe practices to help prevent this information from falling into unauthorized hands.  

#### **_Accuracy and Access  
_**

If you are registered with Mellanox and have obtained a username and password, such information is stored in your profile.  If any of your personally-identifiable information changes or if you want to review the information Mellanox has stored in your profile, you can review and update your profile by contacting [support@mellanox.com](mailto:support@mellanox.com "mailto:support@mellanox.com").  

#### **_Business Transitions    
_**

In the event that Mellanox goes through a business transition, such as a merger, an acquisition by another company, or a sale of all or a portion of its assets, the personal information of our visitors may be shared or transferred.  Visitors will be notified via a prominent notice on this Website for 30 days after a change of ownership or control of Mellanox of the transfer of their personal information if the intended use of their personal information will be contrary to this Privacy Policy.  However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to interfere with the ability of Mellanox to transfer all or part of its business and/or assets (including the Website), for any purposes, without any limitation whatsoever.  Mellanox specifically reserves the right to transfer or share a copy of personally-identifiable information collected from its Website to the buyer of that portion of its business relating to that information.

The information that is collected by Mellanox will be used only for internal business purposes to better serve your needs.  We will not rent, sell, transfer, share or disclose personal information about you with unaffiliated third parties without your prior written consent, except to provide products or services that you have requested or under the following circumstances:

  * We may disclose your personal information in order to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * We may share personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to physical safety of any person, violations of this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We may disclose personal information to our third party service providers who agree to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  Such third party service providers may use your personal information only to provide services to Mellanox and will not be given permission to use such information for other purposes.

#### **_Security_**

We maintain data handling and storage practices and procedures designed to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of customer information. We have security measures implemented in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at this Website.  While we use reasonable efforts to safeguard the security of your personal information, transmissions made on or through the Internet are vulnerable to attack and cannot be guaranteed to be secure.  In addition, submissions made via email are not protected by SSL (Secured Sockets Layer) technology and are vulnerable to interception during transmission.

Nevertheless, when disclosing any personal information via the Internet, there is always the risk that your information may be intercepted without our consent and, consequently, can be collected and used by others without your consent.  In addition, third party sites that are accessed through links on our sites have separate privacy policies and security measures, and Mellanox is not responsible or liable for the practices, policies or security measures implemented on these third party sites.  _You hereby acknowledge that Mellanox is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner_.

#### **_International Users \- Applicable Law_**  

We collect, process, store, disclose and dispose of personal information that you submit to us in accordance with applicable United States law.  Please note that the personal information you submit to our website will be transferred to the United States to be processed by us in order to provide this Website and its services to you or for such other purposes as set forth in this Privacy Policy.  If you are not a resident of the United States, you acknowledge and agree that we may collect and use your personal information, as discussed in this privacy policy, outside your resident jurisdiction.  In addition, we may store such personal information in the United States, outside your resident jurisdiction.  In particular, you are advised that the United States uses a sectoral model of privacy protection that relies on a mix of legislation, governmental regulation and self-regulation.  Please be aware that United States law may offer different levels of protection for personal information than may be available in your country. 

#### **_Intellectual Property  
_**

This Website is protected by U.S. and international copyright and intellectual property laws.  Unless otherwise specified, all information and screens appearing as part of this Website, including software, services, documents, text, images, icons, and logos design; the selection, assembly, arrangement and design thereof, and the code that enables its presentation, are the sole property of Mellanox (collectively, the “Website Materials”).

Except as otherwise required by applicable law, no part of any copyrighted material may be reproduced, modified, translated, distributed, published, or transmitted by any means, electronic or mechanical, for any purpose, without our prior, written authorization or, if owned by a third party, the prior, written authorization of such third party.

Mellanox, Mellanox logo, BridgeX, ConnectX, CORE-Direct, InfiniBridge, InfiniHost, InfiniScale, PhyX, SwitchX, Virtual Protocol Interconnect and Voltaire are registered trademarks of Mellanox Technologies, Ltd. FabricIT, MLNX-OS, Unbreakable-Link, UFM and Unified Fabric Manager are trademarks of Mellanox Technologies, Ltd. All other trademarks are property of their respective owners.

#### **_Code of Ethics  
_**

Mellanox Technologies, Ltd. (the "Company") is dedicated to conducting its business consistent with the highest standards of business ethics. We have an obligation to our employees, shareholders, customers, suppliers, community representatives and other business contacts to be honest, fair and forthright in all of our business activities. 

This Code of Business Conduct and Ethics contains general guidelines for conducting the business of the Company consistent with the highest standards of business ethics. To the extent this Code requires a higher standard than required by commercial practice or applicable laws, rules or regulations, we adhere to these higher standards. 

This Code applies to all of our directors, officers and employees. We refer to all persons covered by this Code as "Company employees" or simply "employees." We also refer to our Chief Executive Officer and our Chief Financial Officer as our "principal financial officers."

#### **_Changes to this Privacy Policy  
_**

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time without notice.  All amended terms shall automatically be effective as soon as they are posted on the Website.  Please review this Privacy Policy often to review any changes that may affect your use of the Website and how your information is used.  Your continued use of the Website indicates your assent to any changes to this Privacy Policy.  

Mellanox shall have the right, in its sole discretion, to change, suspend or discontinue this Website or any aspect of this Website, generally or with respect to you, at any time, including hours of operation and availability of any Website feature, database or content without notice and without liability to you or any third party.

####  **_Opt-out  
_**

If you request to receive communications from us, you will receive information we believe will be of use and interest to you.  ****

#### **_Children  
_**

Children (persons under the age of 18) are not eligible to use this Website unsupervised, and we ask that children do not submit any personal information to us.  If you are under the age of 18, you may only use this Website in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians.

#### **_Contact Us  
_**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [info@mellanox.com](mailto:info@mellanox.com)

Copyright © 1999 - 2014 by Mellanox Technologies, Ltd.  All rights reserved.
